ELABO EVANS

Phone: (+233) 559237619 / (+233) 209273423 Email: <u>ellaboevans@gmail.com</u> Postal Address: P.O BOX 11, Mpataba, Jomoro District, Western Region,

Ghana Residential: House Number M/40, Near Chief Palace, Mpataba.

CAREER OBJECTIVES

As an organized and highly creative individual, I love the challenges of working within a dynamic and fast paced working environment. The knowledge gained from my corporate experience with team mates and groups has shaped my ability to adopt quickly ,work efficiently, think creatively and work efficiently as part of a team or on my own.

INTEREST AND HOBBIES

Reading, Surfing the internet and Listening to music during my leisure periods.

EDUCATION

Kwame Nkrumah University of Science and Technology Bachelor of Art (Linguistics)

Kumasi, Ghana January, 2021 - To date

Nkroful Agricultural SHS

General Art

Western Region, Ghana October, 2016- May, 2019

CORE SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES

Good interpersonal and leadership skills

Self-motivated and target-oriented

Ability to work effectively with a team

OTHER SKILLS

Microsoft Office (Word, Excel and PowerPoint)

Graphics Design (Adobe Photoshop)

Web Design (Wordpress)

WORK EXPERIENCE

March, 2020 - Holy Child Preparatory School, Nzema Aiyinasi, W/R

I was part of the staff of the above mentioned school as a subject teacher at the JHS level before COVID-19 came to set in.

Freelance Graphic Designer, 2018-To Date

I have worked as freelancer for almost 4 years now, since I'm in school and do not get hired.

LEADERSHIP SKILLS

Deputy Editorial Chair

Ghanaian Language Students Association , KNUST July, 2021- To date

Course Rep

KNUST Chinese for Communication Oral course January, 2021 – To date

General Secretary

Nkroful Agricultural SHS, Writers and Debtors club 2019/2020 Academic year

Academic (Prep) Prefect

Nkroful Agricultural SHS 2019/2020 Academic year

<u>REFEREES</u>

Mr. Prince Barfi

Tutor (Nkroful Agricultural SHS)

0246925734

Dr. Obed Nii Broohm

Lecturer (Department of Language and Communication Sciences)

Email: obed.broohm@knust.edu.gh

0242526431